{"sid": "3S2Z9N51U7IA_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 396491, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 396491, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 402298]], "time_left_end": "295", "answered_time": 402298, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "295", "question_time_start": 402298, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 411578]], "time_left_end": "285", "answered_time": 411578, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "285", "question_time_start": 411578, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 416934]], "time_left_end": "280", "answered_time": 416934, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "280", "question_time_start": 416934, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 431526]], "time_left_end": "265", "answered_time": 431526, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "265", "question_time_start": 431526, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["submit", 442068]], "time_left_end": "255", "answered_time": 442068, "user_answer": "802", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "255", "question_time_start": 442068, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["submit", 455926]], "time_left_end": "241", "answered_time": 455926, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "241", "question_time_start": 455926, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 480383]], "time_left_end": "217", "answered_time": 480383, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "217", "question_time_start": 480384, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 489179]], "time_left_end": "208", "answered_time": 489179, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "208", "question_time_start": 489179, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 492822]], "time_left_end": "204", "answered_time": 492822, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "204", "question_time_start": 492822, "question": "7+3+29", "correct_answer": 39, "events": [["submit", 495742]], "time_left_end": "201", "answered_time": 495742, "user_answer": "39", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 495742, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "201", "question_time_start": 495742, "question": "9+78+47", "correct_answer": 134, "events": [["submit", 510309]], "time_left_end": "187", "answered_time": 510309, "user_answer": "134", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "187", "question_time_start": 510309, "question": "16+977", "correct_answer": 993, "events": [["submit", 523634]], "time_left_end": "173", "answered_time": 523634, "user_answer": "993", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "173", "question_time_start": 523634, "question": "4+3+6+74", "correct_answer": 87, "events": [["submit", 533245]], "time_left_end": "164", "answered_time": 533245, "user_answer": "87", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "164", "question_time_start": 533245, "question": "24+24", "correct_answer": 48, "events": [["submit", 537196]], "time_left_end": "160", "answered_time": 537196, "user_answer": "48", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "160", "question_time_start": 537196, "question": "4+6+4+49", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 543176]], "time_left_end": "154", "answered_time": 543176, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "154", "question_time_start": 543176, "question": "6+66+78", "correct_answer": 150, "events": [["submit", 552987]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 552987, "user_answer": "150", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 552988, "question": "8+7+49", "correct_answer": 64, "events": [["submit", 565787]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 565787, "user_answer": "64", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 565787, "question": "37+74", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 575528]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 575527, "user_answer": "111", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 575528, "question": "3+4+6+77", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 580843]], "time_left_end": "116", "answered_time": 580843, "user_answer": "90", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "116", "question_time_start": 580843, "question": "6+8+46", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 588662]], "time_left_end": "108", "answered_time": 588662, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 588662, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "108", "question_time_start": 588662, "question": "9+57+38", "correct_answer": 104, "events": [["submit", 602933]], "time_left_end": "94", "answered_time": 602933, "user_answer": "104", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "94", "question_time_start": 602933, "question": "67+83", "correct_answer": 150, "events": [["submit", 608612]], "time_left_end": "88", "answered_time": 608612, "user_answer": "150", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "88", "question_time_start": 608612, "question": "4+63+28", "correct_answer": 95, "events": [["submit", 617033]], "time_left_end": "80", "answered_time": 617033, "user_answer": "95", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "80", "question_time_start": 617033, "question": "3+7+94", "correct_answer": 104, "events": [["submit", 622506]], "time_left_end": "74", "answered_time": 622506, "user_answer": "104", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "74", "question_time_start": 622507, "question": "43+49", "correct_answer": 92, "events": [["submit", 630683]], "time_left_end": "66", "answered_time": 630683, "user_answer": "92", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "66", "question_time_start": 630683, "question": "8+6+6+78", "correct_answer": 98, "events": [["submit", 640507]], "time_left_end": "56", "answered_time": 640507, "user_answer": "98", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "56", "question_time_start": 640507, "question": "47+428", "correct_answer": 475, "events": [["submit", 654676]], "time_left_end": "42", "answered_time": 654676, "user_answer": "475", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "42", "question_time_start": 654676, "question": "3+4+6+28", "correct_answer": 41, "events": [["submit", 661808]], "time_left_end": "35", "answered_time": 661808, "user_answer": "41", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "35", "question_time_start": 661809, "question": "6+8+6+53", "correct_answer": 73, "events": [["submit", 668856]], "time_left_end": "28", "answered_time": 668856, "user_answer": "73", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "28", "question_time_start": 668856, "question": "8+7+17", "correct_answer": 32, "events": [["submit", 678351]], "time_left_end": "19", "answered_time": 678351, "user_answer": "32", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 678351, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "19", "question_time_start": 678351, "question": "36+154", "correct_answer": 190, "events": [["submit", 684551]], "time_left_end": "12", "answered_time": 684551, "user_answer": "190", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "12", "question_time_start": 684551, "question": "8+7+7+86", "correct_answer": 108, "events": [["submit", 692751]], "time_left_end": "4", "answered_time": 692751, "user_answer": "108", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "4", "question_time_start": 692751, "question": "7+8+7+69", "correct_answer": 91, "events": []}}}}}